webdeveloperplus.com 2016-10-31

# Privacy Policy | Web Developer Plus

Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

WebDeveloperPlus may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

#### Information we gather and track

The type of personal information we collect are:

  * Name (Comments)
  * Website URl (optional) (Comments)
  * Email address (Comments)
  * Google AdSense that stores tracking cookies on your computer
  * 3rd party advertisements that may store tracking cookies on your computer to recognize repeated visits (only)
  * Tracking cookies by various traffic counting services for statistical purposes – this data is not traceable back to you except for your IP address

#### How we use Cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computerâ€™s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

WebDeveloperPlus may use cookies to keep some information that are placed by a Web site in a storage place on your own computer. We use cookies to track usage patterns on the site. Our cookies do not contain personally identifiable information and such cookies are not shared with any third party.

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

#### DoubleClick DART Cookies

WebDeveloperPlus.com may also use DART cookies for ad serving through Googleâ€™s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google Adsense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests which are also known as â€œinterest based targetingâ€. The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (for example, if you have been viewing sites about food, you may see advertisements related to recipes, food, and cooking utensils when viewing a non-related site, such as a site about travel). DART uses non personally identifiable information. It does not track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

You can always choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a website running the advertisements, a new cookie will automatically be added again.

####  How we use Collected Information

The name and website URl are displayed on comments, but email address is secure with us. We do not share it with outside parties. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

#### How to Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please use the [Contact Us](http://webdeveloperplus.com/contact/) form.
